Justin Brown

SKILLS

Programming: SQL, Python, C++

Data Visualization: Advanced in Excel, Google Sheets, R. Proficient using Tableau and git.

Server: Amazon Web Server, and Digital Ocean hosting a Linux based, docker installed database. Using PuTTY, and SSH.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Versatile individual with experience collecting, transforming, and organizing data for analysis to help make informed decisions. Excellent understanding and proficiency of platforms for effective data analyses, including SQL, spreadsheets, Tableau, and R. Strong Communication, organizational, and analytical skills. Recently completed the Google Data Analytics Certificate – a rigorous, hands-on program that covers the entire scope of the data analysis process.

EXPERIENCE

JustinBrown Drone Photography, Chicago — CEO

February 2018 - Current

- FAA Certified 107 Drone Operator
- Filmed Chicago Marathon Commercial for Nike
- Exclusive drone pilot to the Chicago Botanical Gardens

Brown & Associates, Chicago - Office Manager

February 2014 - November 2018

- Transcribing and managing confidential information for CEO
- Created file structure system for policy and procedure manuals.

EDUCATION

Fullsail University, Winterpark Florida - Bachelor of Science,

Game Design and Development

June 2012 - October 2014, Online

Google Data Analytics Professional Certificate

Coursera: Python for Everyone

Coursera: Twitter Sentiment Analysis